http://www.amanikids.org/amani/privacy

Privacy Policy
Our commitment to privacy: Amani Children’s Home knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate you trusting that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This Privacy Policy explains our practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used by Amani Children’s Home. It applies to donor information that we collect both online and offline.
What information is collected by Amani Children’s Home? We collect personal information when you voluntarily submit it to us.
For example, donors may provide us with personal information (such as name, address, email address, telephone numbers and/or credit/debit card information). If a donor, or a website visitor, contacts us by email they may provide us with their email address, and name. Providing data is required in these contexts in order for us to process your donations, requests, or respond to inquiries.
In addition to the personal information that you submit to us, we may collect personal information about you from reputable third parties, or automatically collect information using the following technologies:
Web Server Logs. Our web servers may collect certain information such as IP address, pages visited, time of visits, and referring website.
Cookies. Cookies are simple text files stored by your web browser that provide a method of distinguishing among donors and visitors to the website. Amani Children’s Home uses cookies to identify your browser as you visit pages on the Amani Children’s Home website.
Where do we transfer and store information? Amani Children’s Home is based in Tanzania and its website is hosted in the United States, and any information transmitted to us may be stored, accessed, or processed in the United States. Residents of some other countries, including residents of the European Union, should be aware that the laws of the United States do not offer the same protections as the laws of your home country.
How do we use information? We collect information primarily to accept donations, complete our charitable projects, and provide you with information concerning our programs, projects, and activities. We also use information for analytical purposes, to improve our website, our donor base, our outreach, or to respond to requests for information or merchandise. We may inform you of other purposes at the time that we collect some forms of information. For example, if you apply for a job we may collect information in order to process your job application.
With whom do we share information? We do not trade, share, or sell information that you provide to us with other organizations who intend to use it only to market their products or services to you. There may be instances in which we share your information with others. We may share your information, for example, in conjunction with your sponsorship of a certain project, as required by law, with law enforcement, to comply with legal process, to protect our legal rights, to protect the safety or security of a person, or to protect against fraud, criminal acts, or misconduct. We may also share your information with companies that provide us with services, or with a successor legal entity.
Our commitment to data security To help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect.
Your access to data, and your choices If you would like to access the data that we received from you, or make corrections to it, you may contact us at the email or mailing addresses provided at the end of this policy. If you registered to receive communications from us and later change your mind, you may ask that your name and contact information be removed from our distribution list. You can send such a request to the email or mailing addresses at the end of this policy. Some web browsers and devices permit you to broadcast a preference that you not be “tracked” online. At this time we do not modify your experience based upon whether such a signal is broadcast.
Additional information
Behavioral Advertising. We may participate in behavioral-based advertising. This means that a third party may use technology (e.g., a cookie) to collect information about your use of our website so that they can provide advertising about products and services tailored to your interest. That advertising may appear either on our website, or on other websites.
Links. Our website may contain links to other Web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are entering another site that is governed by that site’s privacy policy.
Changes to this privacy statement. We may modify this privacy policy from time to time. Any changes will be reflected on this website. If we make a material change to this policy, and need to apply it to personal information that you provided to us before the change was made, we will attempt to contact you and obtain your consent to the change.
Communicating with us. If we need, or are required to, contact you about the privacy or security of your information we may do so by telephone, email, or mail. If you have any questions, concerns, requests, or comments about privacy, you can contact us.
Follow on Facebook
Follow on Twitter
Follow our Blog
Why AmaniThe Amani Children
What We DoRescuing Children
Giving Primary Care
Educating Kids
Reuniting Families
Privacy PolicyRegistered Charity No. Tanzania NGO-0766 Amani Children's Home
